South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Hallelujah!
Lord I come to You
Let my heart be changed, renewed
Flowing from the grace that I found in You
Lord I come to know
The weaknesses I see in me
Will be stripped away
By the blood of the Lamb
Hold me close
Let Your love surround me
Bring me near
Draw me to Your side
And as I wait I'll rise like an eagle
And I will soar with You
Your Spirit leads me on
By the power of Your love
Hold me close
Let Your love surround me
Bring me near
Draw me to Your side
And as I wait I'll rise like an eagle
And I will soar with You
Your Spirit leads me on
By the power of Your love
Hold me close
Let Your love surround me
Bring me near
Draw me to Your side
South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
And I will soar with You
Your Spirit leads me on
By the power of Your love
Hallelujah!
You may be seated. Thank you. Hallelujah!
South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Good Morning!
Viewers, Good Morning!
Viewers all over the world, Good Morning!
Hallelujah!
South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
This is just a word of exhortation.
So let's take our Bible to the Book of Psalm.
The Book of Psalm 66:18.
"If I had cherished sin in my heart, the Lord would not have listened."
Let's take our Bible also to the Book of Matthew 5.
It's related to that Book of Psalm 66:18.
Let's read verse 8.
"Blessed are the pure in heart, for they will see Jesus."
It's all about heart.
Psalm 66:18 says: "If I cherish iniquity in my heart, the Lord will not hear me."
In this Matthew 5:8 it says:
"Blessed are the pure in heart..."
Take note: If I cherish iniquity in my heart,
the Lord will not hear me.
Heart, heart, heart...
What does this mean to us?
It means the greatest thing the Lord looks into is our heart.
The greatest thing, the most cherished thing the Lord looks into is our heart.
We are made in our hearts to be like Jesus.
Whatever colour, race, appearance - it does not matter.
Whether you are black, yellow, red - whatever colour - the judgment will be based on our heart,
that is the content of our character.
Yes.
We are made in our hearts to be like Him.
If you cherish iniquity in your heart, the Lord will not hear you.
This is why only faith pleases God and the faith is of man's heart.
When we say 'heart', we mean 'the spirit of man' - biblically.
Heart.
Whatever appearance, colour, race - it does not matter.
With a pure heart, a man knows that Jesus is Lord.
With a pure heart, man knows that Jesus is righteousness.
With a pure heart, man knows that Jesus saves.
With a pure heart, man knows that Jesus heals.
If you cherish iniquity, that is sin, if your honour iniquity in your heart,
the Lord will not listen to you.
God listens, Jesus listens as you pray and He replies in relation to the state of your heart.
You say: "Jesus, Jesus, Jesus! Help me, Jesus!.."
He listens, replies in relation to the state of your heart.
If you hold grudges in your heart and you are saying "Jesus", you are wasting your time.
If you hold offence and you are saying "Jesus", you are wasting your time.
South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
If you hold offence in your heart, don't be surprised if the Bible will make no meaning to you.
If you hold offence such as bitterness, grudges, anger, hatred and so forth and you open the Bible
and you hold offence against someone, against anyone and you are reading Bible, you are wasting your time.
You are reading literature.
This is The Book of books.
When you are reading it, you are reading the Holy Spirit.
Heart.
If we know we are made in our heart to be like Jesus, why are we fighting over colour?
Why short, why high? Why big stomach, why small stomach?
I want to be like Jesus in my heart.
If you hold offence in your heart, don't be surprised that your prayer will not be accepted.
My heart! Yes.
Christianity lies in the heart.
Finally, I will take you to the Book of Romans.
Romans 9:1.
"I speak the truth in Christ - I am not lying, my conscience confirms it through the Holy Spirit."
Today, the conscience is ignored,
which is the very instrument the Holy Spirit uses
to ride us, to push us and to guide us.
We ignore the conscience.
Today, we talk about the Holy Spirit, whereas the conscience - your heart,
which the Holy Spirit uses as a guide to the soul is ignored.
In order to pray effectively, there must not be anything between us and God.
The conscience we ignore is the very root, the very instrument the Holy Spirit uses to guide us.
So you say: "Holy, holy, holy!" whereas the heart is full of iniquity, holding grudges, holding hatred.
"Holy!.." - first talk to your heart.
When the Holy Spirit comes, if the heart is not free, it can't attract the Spirit of God.
We must allow our spirit to be free from grudges, hatred, bitterness before we can say: "Holy!"
If not, the Holy Spirit will come and move round without attending to you.
Our heart is the contact point, the communication point for the Holy Spirit
If the contact point is not free...
Your heart is the communication point; take care of your heart.
Free your heart from offence such as grudges, hatred and bitterness.
Free your heart!
You must free your heart.
Stop ignoring your heart.
It is the contact point of the Holy Spirit.
Tell your neighbour.
Stop ignoring your heart; it's the contact point of the Holy Spirit.
South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Contact point of the Holy Spirit.
It is essential for every Christian to be free of offence.
What you are facing today is a result of offence.
Offence has opened the door to the various situations in your life.
Yes, that is offence.
Christianity lies in the heart.
Viewers, thank you.
South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
I was trying to counsel you yesterday concerning the issue of healing and deliverance.
It's not only healing or deliverance, help from God. If God sends you to help your neighbour,
the help that comes from the heart - we don't give that help first before you receive reward.
Let me give you a good example; issue of healing, deliverance and all of God's blessings.
No one can give money from the heart, before healing is given.
No one can give money from the heart before healing.
You can give money but that money is not from the heart.
No one can give money from the heart before healing and God's blessings.
And anything given that is not from the heart is a sin.
If you give me this and it is not from your heart, it will not bless me.
I would use it but it will not bless my life.
But if you now give me from your heart, it will bless me and bless my future.
Money should not be exchanged for God's blessing.
If I deliver you and you are free, whatever you give me after that will come from your heart.
And it will bless my life, now and forever.
God has a way of talking to people's hearts.
Healing, deliverance and all of God's blessings are hindered by the way and manner
we go about the issue of money.
That is why you see the fire of revival is going down.
The fire of revival is going down.
When we give freely as we are given by God, God will raise His people to bless you in abundance.
When it is time for revival, it is time for sacrifice.
It's always good to sacrifice first before receiving.
Sacrifice means labour before reward. By the time reward comes, it will come in a way
that will bless your career, your future forever.
God bless you. This is my message and I will continue to preach this anywhere.
Hallelujah!
South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
TT Monica Asefa 27/02/19
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 17/03/2019